postjoint.com 2013-05-23

# PostJoint - Terms of Service

## Privacy Policy

We respect the privacy of your personal information. This policy sets out how we use any personal information collected from you when using our service. For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the Act), the data controller is PostJoint Limited.

#### Information Collection

We collect information about you that you provide by filling in forms on this site. This includes information which you provide when registering to use the service, if you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence and when you visit this site. 

By using our site you are giving us permission to use your personal information in the ways set out in this Privacy Policy.

We do not store or have access to any of your payment, credit card or bank details. All transactions are processed by our third party payment service.

#### Use of your information

We use your information to provide our services to you and to support your relationship with us, and, if you agree, to send you information about other services we think may be of interest to you. We use your information collected from this site to personalise your repeat visits to this site. We do not disclose or sell your information outside our corporate group.

#### Marketing

We will use your information to send you information about products, services, promotions and events which may be of interest to you.

#### Disclosure of your information

We will never disclose your personal information to third parties, unless:

  * we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal information to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets;
  * our assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal information held by it about its users and customers will be one of the transferred assets;
  * we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal information in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of service; or to protect the rights of our customers, employees or the general public.

#### Security

All personal information you provide to us is stored on secure servers. Where we have given you a password which enables you to access certain areas of this site you are responsible for keeping that password confidential and the password should not be shared with anyone. We may need to transfer your personal information to the USA where our secure servers are located.

#### Cookies

In order to improve this site, we use "cookies" to track your visit. A cookie is a small amount of data that is placed on your computer to collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour information. This information is used to track visitor use of our site and to compile statistical reports on website activity. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. However, please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this site.

#### Links to other websites

This site may contain links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this site so when you link to other websites you should read their privacy policies.

#### Your rights

You have the right to ask us not to use your personal information for marketing purposes. You can exercise this right by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by [ contacting us](http://support.postjoint.com/) or writing to PostJoint, Unit 22 Grenville Workshops, London, N19 4EH, UK.

#### Access to information

The Data Protection Act gives you rights to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with these details.

#### Changes to this privacy policy

Any changes we make to our privacy policy will be posted on this page and where appropriate notified to you by e-mail.

Last updated 27 Sept 2012
